Hello friends, welcome to our channel.
Today I am going to talk about
how to activate iBank's internet banking for the first time. So if you also have a
bank account in iBank and want to
activate your iBank internet banking, then how
can you activate it here? How do you
activate it here? I am going to tell you
in detail through the latest process here. If
you
watch the video completely, you will also
know in detail here how to activate iBank's internet banking for the
first time.
Friends, let's start the video. To
activate net banking,
open any browser. Next, you have to
type ICICI net banking here,
as you can see here.
You have to type this, after that click in the search bar.
Next, you will
see internet banking, net banking,
online banking, iBank, so what do you have to do?
Click on this, after that
you will see a cross here,
click on the cross, after that you will
get the option to log in at both places,
as you can see login here
and  You can see Login Now here,
you can click anywhere on both of them.
If you are doing it on mobile,
you will see Login Now in the middle here.
So what you have to do is click on it.
If you want to come directly to this page,
I have given its link below this video,
you can come directly to this page by clicking on it. If you
want to open it on mobile,
you can see it here on the side. In this way the
interface will open. There will be no problem.
If you have a mobile, then
next you will see Get User
ID here. So what you have to do is click on this.
Next you will
get many options in the same way. If you have a
normal bank account, then what you have to do is
click on this. If you have a
credit card, then click on this.
If you have a travel card, then
click on this. If you have a loan
account number, then also you
can activate internet banking here by clicking on this.
If you have a joined account,
then what you have to do is click on this. The
process is the same here, so
my here  This is a normal bank account, that is
why I clicked on the
check box that is visible in front of the bank account.
What to do after that is to
fill up your bank account number here. Now
after filling up the bank account number, you will
see the verify tick here in the same way as
you can see here. Next,
whatever mobile number is linked to your bank account,
you have to fill up the same mobile number here. After
filling up the mobile number, it will be
visible here. So
what to do is to click on it.
After doing this much, a
new interface will open in the same way.
After that, what you have to do is to come down a little.
After coming down, you will see the image
of the back side of a debit card here
and some letters will be written inside the small box.
So what you have to do is that the
digits, the letters, what you have to do is to
come down. You can
see it here. My CDM is
coming separately here, it will come separately for you, so
what you have to do
You have to check on the back side of your debit card what is in box A and
what is in box B, then
you have to fill up accordingly.
Now after filling up, you will
see Go here, click on Go.
Now it is being said here that your
user ID has been sent to the mobile number linked to your bank account,
after that what we have to do is
create a password here. Now to
create a password, you will
see here 'Generate Login Password', so
what to do is click on it.
Next, you will see Click Here here,
so what to do is click on it.
Now whatever user ID
you had received, you have to fill up the same user ID here.
After that, you have to fill up the
same mobile number which is linked with your bank account.
Now after filling up all the details, you will
see Go here,
click on Go. After that,
an OTP will come to you on the same mobile number linked to your bank account. You have to
fill up the OTP here.  After that you will
see Authenticate here, so what you have to do is
click on it, next
you have to scroll down a little here,
again you have to follow the same process here, there will be
small boxes on the back side of your debit card,
whatever digits are inside the boxes, you have to fill up the same in all the three boxes as per
your wish,
what is in box A, what is in box B,
what is in box C, you have to fill up here,
after that you have to click on submit here,
after doing this much work
you will see your user ID here,
after that you will see new
password here, so what you have to do is
you have to create a password here as per your wish,
which should be unique, for example
I have given it above, so in the same way
you have to create a new password here,
next you will see confirm
new password here, so what you have to do,
whatever password you have created above,
you have to fill up the same password here,
after that you will see update here, you have to
click on update, now you can see it here on
our  It has been successful,
next you will see login now here,
so what to do is click on it,
now you can see here,
after doing this much work it will redirect you to the
front page, after that what to do is
whatever your user ID is, you have to
fill it up here, now the login
password which you had created, you have to
fill it up here, next you will
see login here, click on login,
after doing this much work,
whatever internet banking you have will be logged in here in this way, for the
first time a
notification will appear here in the same way as
you can see here, so
what you have to do is click on the cross here,
after that you have to keep doing next next here,
otherwise you will
see skip here, here you
can also click on skip, now you
can see here that whatever internet
banking we have has been activated here,
after that you can check the balance here,
download the statement, if you
want to transfer funds to someone, you
can also transfer funds, so if you also want to
activate internet banking  You have to
activate it in this way, friends, this
was a small information, if you
liked the information then do not forget to like, share and comment.